Yuqing Zhu

yuqingzhu@ucsb.edu https://jeremy43.github.io/

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interest is learning theory, including differential privacy [1, 2, 3, 4, 7], domain adaptation [5, 6] and off-policy reinforcement learning. I am also the co-creator of AutoDP, an open-source library that allows researchers to use advanced mechanisms in differential privacy and obtain strong guarantees correctly.

EDUCATION

University of California, Santa Barbara

2018.09- now

Ph.D. in Computer Science

Nanjing University

2014.09-2018.06

B.S in Computer Science National Elite Program

REWARDS

2021 Google PhD Fellowship Recipient

PUBLICATION AND PREPRINT

[1] Improving Sparse Vector Technique with Renyi Differential Privacy

Yuqing Zhu and Yu-Xiang Wang.

Thirty-fourth Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS-2020).

[2] Private-kNN: Practical Differential Privacy for Computer Vision

Yuqing Zhu, Xiang Yu, Manmohan Chandraker, Yu-Xiang Wang

Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR-2020).

[3] Poisson Subsampled Renyi Differential Privacy

Yuqing Zhu and Yu-Xiang Wang

36th International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML-2019).

[4] Revisiting Model-Agnostic Private Learning: Faster Rates and Active Learning

Chong Liu, Yuqing Zhu, Kamalika Chaudhuri and Yu-Xiang Wang

Accepted by AISTATS-2021 and JMLR-2022.

[5] Model-Agnostic Private Learning with Domain Adaptation

Yuqing Zhu, Chong Liu and Yu-Xiang Wang

CSS Theory and Practice of Differential Privacy Workshop (TPDP-2020).

[6] Voting-based Approaches For Differentially Private Federated Learning

Yuqing Zhu, Xiang Yu, Yi-Hsuan Tsai, Francesco Pittaluga, Masoud Faraki, Manmohan chandraker, Yu-Xiang Wang

[7] Optimal Accounting of Differential Privacy via Characteristic Function

Yuqing Zhu, Jinshuo Dong, Yu-Xiang Wang

CSS Theory and Practice of Differential Privacy Workshop (TPDP-2021).

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Google Research, Federated Learning Team

2021.06 - 2021.09

Advisor: Shanshan Wu and Galen Andrew

· Investigated weighting approaches in differentially private federated learning.

NEC Laboratories America, Media Analytics

Advisor: Dr. Xiang Yu

2020.06 - 2020.09

San Jose, CA

· Differentially private federated learning

Proposed a voting-based solution for differentially private federated learning. See Publication [6].

Microsoft Research Asia (MSRA) Visual Computing Group

2017.06 - 2017.11

Advisor: Dr. Jifeng Dai

MSRA, Beijing, China

· Video Instance-aware segmentation

Created an Official Implementation for Flow-Guided-Feature-Aggregation, and the git repo has already accumulated **500 stars**.github

LAMDA Lab

2016.05 - 2017.09

Advisor: Prof. Wu-Jun LI, Prof. Zhi-Hua Zhou

NJU, Nanjing, China

· Proposed a deep discrete hybrid recommendation system for image & text recommendation.

ACADEMIC SERVICE

Reviewer: NeurIPS-21, AISTATS-21, ICLR-20, ICML-20, ICML-19, UAI-19, NeurIPS-19

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Computer Languages

Python, C, Matlab

Deep Learning Frameworks

Pytorch/Tensorflow/MXNet/Caffee